Guide to the John Nolen Papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
Nolen, John papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
- Series IV. Professional Career
  - Other Professional Activities, and Public Works
    - Public Lectures Illustrated by Slides
      - Wash, ongoing, on Streets, Reading, PA, Z141 (Box 214)
      - Scranton, PA, Map, Z142 (Box 214)
      - City Improvement Association, Scranton, PA, Z143 (Box 214)
      - Railroad Approach, Lancaster, PA, Z144 (Box 214)
      - Railroad Station, Lancaster, PA, Z145 (Box 214)
      - Church & Telephone Poles, Lancaster, PA, Z146 (Box 214)
      - Queen Street (Main Business Grade Crossing) Lancaster, PA, Z147 (Box 214)
      - Post Office Corner, Lancaster, PA, Z148 (Box 214)
      - Penn Square, Lancaster, PA, Z149 (Box 214)
      - City Hall, Penn Square, Lancaster, PA, Z150 (Box 214)
      - City Plan, Lancaster, PA, Z151 (Box 215)
      - Modern Houses, Outskirts, Lancaster, PA, Z152 (Box 215)
      - Approach to Steamboat Landing, Erie, PA, Z153 (Box 215)
      - Erie, PA, Lake Front, Z154 (Box 215)
      - Citiey of Erie, PA, Plan, Z155 (Box 215)
      - Wilmington, DE, Delaware River, Z156 (Box 215)
      - Wilmington, DE, Christina River, Z157 (Box 215)
      - Wilmington, DE, Street Scene with litter, Z158 (Box 215)
      - Location of Wilmington, DE, Z159 (Box 215)
      - Wilmington, DE, Map of City, Z160 (Box 215)
      - Lindens, Massachusetts Ave. Washington D.C., Z161 (Box 215)
      - Roanoke, VA, Tinker Creek, Z162 (Box 215)
      - Roanoke, VA, Dump, Z163 (Box 215)
      - Rubbish, Main Street, Roanoke, Va, Z164 (Box 215)
      - Amusement Park, Roanoke, VA, Z165 (Box 215)
      - Amusement Park, Roanoke, VA, Z166 (Box 215)
      - Amusement Park, Roanoke, VA, Z167 (Box 215)
      - Fall Festival, Roanoke, VA, Z168 (Box 215)
      - Lynchburg, VA, Jones River from Lover's Leap, Z169 (Box 215)
      - Lynchburg, VA, Rivermont Residences, Z170 (Box 215)
      - Lynchburg, VA Randolph Macon Woman's College, Z171 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Lombardy Poplars, Z172 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, North Tryon St., Z173 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Fifth St. near Independence Park, Z174 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Fifth St. near Independence Park, Z175 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Fifth St. near Poplar, Z176 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Cemetery Square, Z177 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Vance Square, Z178 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Boundary of Independence Park, Z179 (Box 215)
      - Plan, Independence Park, Charlotte, NC, Z180 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Plan, 1901; Z181 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC Township, Z182 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, Houses in Piedmont Park, Z183 (Box 215)
      - Water Oak, Charlotte, NC, Z184 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, First Presbyterian Church, Z185 (Box 215)
      - Charlotte, NC, First Presbyterian Church, Z186 (Box 215)
      - Panorama, Pinehurst, NC, City Planning, Z187 (Box 215)
      - Charleston, SC, Residences on Waterfront, Z188 (Box 215)
      - Charleston, SC, Street View, Z189 (Box 215)
      - Charleston, SC, St. Philip's Church, Z190 (Box 215)
      - Chicora Park Plan, Charleston, SC, Z191 (Box 215)
      - Boone Square, Louisville, KY, Z192 (Box 215)
      - Louisville, KY, Central Park Plan, Z193 (Box 215)
      - Map of Memphis, TN, Z194 (Box 215)
      - Tuskegee Institute, AL, Z195 (Box 215)
      - Our Tennessee River, Walden's Ridge, Chattanooga, TN, Z196 (Box 215)
      - South Chickamauga Creek, Chattanooga, TN, Z197 (Box 215)
      - South Chickamauga Creek, Chattanooga, TN, Z198 (Box 215)
      - South Chickamauga Creek, Chattanooga, TN, Z199 (Box 215)
      - Chattanooga Creek, Z201 (Box 216)
      - Tennessee River Front, Chattanooga, TN, Z202 (Box 216)
      - Street at Incline, S. Elmo, Chattanooga, TN, Z204 (Box 216)
      - East Lake Park, Chattanooga, TN, Z205 (Box 216)
      - Olympia Park, Chattanooga, TN, Z206 (Box 216)
      - Jackson Park, Chattanooga, TN, Z207 (Box 216)
      - Cameron Hill, Boynton Park, Chattanooga, TN, Z208 (Box 216)
      - Lookout Mountain Incline, Chattanooga, TN, Z209 (Box 216)
      - Mocassin Bend, Chattanooga, TN, Z210 (Box 216)
      - Missionary Ridge, Chattanooga, TN, Z211 (Box 216)
      - On Missionary Ridge, Chattanooga, TN, Z212 (Box 216)
      - Bragg's Headquarter, Missionary Ridge, Chattanooga, TN, Z213 (Box 216)
      - On Walden's Ridge Road, Chattanooga, TN, Z214 (Box 216)
      - Live Oaks, Savannah, GA, Z215 (Box 216)
      - Euclid Ave Arcade, Cleveland, OH, Z216 (Box 216)
      - Bar Room Scene Gambling, Cleveland, OH, Z217 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, Dayton, OH, Z218 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, Niles, MI, Z219 (Box 216)
      - Map of Grand Rapids, MI, Z220 (Box 216)
      - Map of South Bend, IN, Z221 (Box 216)
      - Industrial Map of South Bend, IN, Z222 (Box 216)
      - La Crosse, WI Railroad Station, Chicago and NorthWest Railroad, Z223 (Box 216)
      - Chicago, IL, Michigan Avenue, Z224 (Box 216)
      - Chicago, IL, School Playground, Z225 (Box 216)
      - Chicago, IL, School Playground, Z226 (Box 216)
      - Couch? House, Milwaukee, WI, Z227 (Box 216)
      - Convention Hall, Milwaukee, WI, Z228 (Box 216)
      - City Map, Milwaukee, WI, Z229 (Box 216)
      - Proposed Plan for Milwaukee, WI, Z230 (Box 216)
      - Milwaukee, WI, West of County Viaduct, Z231 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, C & NW, Madison, WI, Z232 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, C & NW, Madison, WI, Z233 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station and Lake, Madison, WI, Z234 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, C & NW, Madison, WI, Z235 (Box 216)
      - Approach to Madison, WI, Marsh, Z236 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Approach to Madison, WI, 1910; Z237 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Approach to Madison, WI, 1910; Z238 (Box 216)
      - Railroad Station, C & NW, Madison, WI, Z239 (Box 216)
      - State Street, Madison, WI, Z240 (Box 216)
      - Street Trees, Madison, WI, Z241 (Box 216)
      - East Washington Ave, Approach to Capitol, Madison, WI, Z242 (Box 216)
      - Madison, WI, The Old Capitol, Z243 (Box 216)
      - Near State Capitol, Madison, WI, 1910; Z244 (Box 216)
      - View from State Capitol, Madison, WI, 1910; Z245 (Box 216)
      - East Washington Ave Approach, Madison, WI, Z246 (Box 216)
      - Near Capitol and Washington, Z247 (Box 216)
      - New WI State Capitol Pediment, Z248 (Box 216)
      - Section, Capitol Approach, Madison, WI, Z249 (Box 216)
      - Back Yard, Madison, WI, 1910; Z250 (Box 216)
      - Back Yard, Madison, WI, Z251 (Box 217)
      - Madison, WI, Coming to Terriotorial Legislature Session, 1840; Z252 (Box 217)
      - Northwestern Station, La Crosse, WI, Z253 (Box 217)
      - Waterfront, La Crosse, WI, Z254 (Box 217)
      - Riverfront, La Crosse, WI, Z255 (Box 217)
      - Fourth St, La Crosse, WI, Z256 (Box 217)
      - No Wires, La Crosse, WI, Pearl St East from Third, Z257 (Box 217)
      - Stoddard Hotel, La Crosse, WI, Z258 (Box 217)
      - High School, La Crosse, WI, Z259 (Box 217)
      - La Crosse, WI Playground, Z260 (Box 217)
      - Approach, Granddad Bluff, La Crosse, WI, Z261 (Box 217)
      - Approach, Granddad Bluff, La Crosse, WI, Z262 (Box 217)
      - Bluff Scenery, La Crosse, WI, Z263 (Box 217)
      - River Bluff & Golf Club, La Crosse, WI, Z264 (Box 217)
      - Pettibone Park, La Crosse, WI, Z265 (Box 217)
      - View at Railroad Station, Elroy, WI, Z266 (Box 217)
      - Rairoad Station, Elroy, WI, Z267 (Box 217)
      - Dunlap Square, Marinette, WI, Z268 (Box 217)
      - Map of Marinette, WI, Z269 (Box 217)
      - Map of Wisconsin, Z270 (Box 217)
      - Levee Park, Winona, MN, Z271 (Box 217)
      - State Capitol, Des Moines, IA, Z272 (Box 217)
      - Business Street, Western State, Kansas City?, Z273 (Box 217)
      - Denver, CO, State Capitol, Z274 (Box 217)
      - Antlers Hotel, Colorado Springs, CO, Z275 (Box 217)
      - Garden of Gods, Colorado Springs, CO, Z276 (Box 217)
      - Salt Lake City, UT, Main Street, Telephone Poles, Z277 (Box 217)
      - Salt Lake City, UT, Street Poles Removed, Z278 (Box 217)
      - San Francisco, CA, Two Years After Earthquake, Z279 (Box 217)
      - El Caramel Mission, Monterey, CA, Z280 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Santa Fe Railroad Station, 1908; Z281 (Box 217)
      - The Bay, San Diego, CA, Z282 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Atlantic Street, North of D. Street, 1908; Z283 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Fifth St. from D. Street, Z284 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Coronado Ferry, Trolley Line, Z285 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Atlantic St. South of D. Street, Z286 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, D St. looking East, 1908; Z287 (Box 217)
      - Fifth St. at D. St, San Diego, CA, looking South, 1908; Z288 (Box 217)
      - Design for Telephone Poles, San Diego, "D" Street, Z289 (Box 217)
      - University School, San Diego, CA, Z290 (Box 217)
      - Torrey Pines, San Diego, CA, Z291 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Plan, Good Topography, Z292 (Box 217)
      - San Diego, CA, Plan of Boulevards, Z293 (Box 217)
      - Florence Heights & Bay, San Diego, CA, Z294 (Box 217)
      - Old Mission, San Diego, CA, Z295 (Box 217)
      - Torrey Pines, San Diego, CA, Z296 (Box 217)
      - George Street, Halifax. Canada, Z297 (Box 217)
      - University Ave, Toronto, Canada, Z298 (Box 217)
      - Their only Playground, the Churchyard, Z299 (Box 217)
      - A ragged children's picnic to the seashore., Z300 (Box 217)
      - Dulham Park, the Children's Playground, London, England, Z301 (Box 218)
      - Modern Chapel, Shalford Hamlet Surrey, England, Z302 (Box 218)
      - Tintern Abbey, England, Z303 (Box 218)
      - Map of Switzerland, Z304 (Box 218)
      - Royal Palm Trees, Botanical Garden, Havana, Cuba, Z305 (Box 218)
      - Vaphio Cups, Mycenean Age, Z306 (Box 218)
      - Antique Kazak, Size 5.9 x 7.2, Z307 (Box 218)
      - Gute Nacht, Theodor Grust, Z308 (Box 218)
      - Charles River, MA, Canoe Map, Z309 (Box 218)
      - Waterfront, Boston from Boston Herald, January 1, 1912; Z310 (Box 218)
      - Real Boston, Plan, 1911; Z311 (Box 218)
      - Riverfront, Springfield, MA, Z312 (Box 218)
      - Residence Park, Springfield, MA, Z313 (Box 218)
      - Springfield, MA, Municipal Buildings, December 1911; Z314 (Box 218)
      - Railroad Bridge, Main St. Springfield, MA, Z315 (Box 218)
      - Main Street, Springfield, MA, Z316 (Box 218)
      - Main Street, Springfield, MA, Z317 (Box 218)
      - Transportation & Commercial Map, Springfield, MA, 1909; Z318 (Box 218)
      - Bevington St. Area, Liverpool, UK, Z319 (Box 218)
      - Plan, Monckebergstrasse, Hamburg Rathaus, Germany, Z320 (Box 218)
      - Cartoon, Which better typifies Boston, MA, Z321 (Box 218)
      - Harbor & Presque Isle, Erie, PA, Z322 (Box 218)
      - Oliver Hazard Perry, Erie, PA, Z323 (Box 218)
      - Perry leaving the Lawrence, Lake Erie, 1813; Z324 (Box 218)
      - Too Much Perry, Cartoon, Erie, PA, Z325 (Box 218)
      - Proposed Street Changes, Worcester, MA, Z326 (Box 218)
      - Junction, Main and Pleasant Streets, Worcester, MA, Z327 (Box 218)
      - Map of Fitchburg, MA, Z328 (Box 218)
      - Opposite Railroad Station, Fitchburg, MA, Z329 (Box 218)
      - Main Street, Goodnow Co. Fitchburg, MA, Z330 (Box 218)
      - Main Street, Building Line Problem, Fitchburg, MA, Z331 (Box 218)
      - Opposite Principal Club, Main Street, Fitchburg, MA, Z332 (Box 218)
      - Environment, Public Buildings, Fitchburgh, MA, Z333 (Box 218)
      - Environment, Public Buildings, Fitchburgh, MA, Z334 (Box 218)
      - Mass Ave Plans, building line, Cambridge, MA, Z335 (Box 218)
      - Central Square, Cambridge, MA, Z336 (Box 218)
      - Map of Lock Haven, PA, Proposed Improvements, Z337 (Box 218)
      - West Water Street, Lock Haven, PA, Z338 (Box 218)
      - Street Intersection, Lock Haven, PA, Z339 (Box 218)
      - Playground Site, Lock Haven, PA, Z340 (Box 218)
      - River View, Lock Haven, PA, Z341 (Box 218)
      - River View, Susquehanna, Opposite, Lock Haven, PA, Z342 (Box 218)
      - Susquehanna River, Lock Haven, PA, Z343 (Box 218)
      - Bald Eagle Creek, Lock Haven, PA, Z344 (Box 218)
      - Three Magnets, Lock Haven, PA, Z345 (Box 218)
      - Main Street, Lock Haven, Before & After, Z346 (Box 218)
      - Street Standard, Lock Haven, PA, Z347 (Box 218)
      - Street Fixtures, Lock Haven, PA, Z348 (Box 218)
      - Old Bridge House, Lock Haven, PA, Before & After, Z349 (Box 218)
      - Presbyterian Alley, Lock Haven, PA Before & After, Z350 (Box 218)
      - Land Lighthouse, City Park, Erie, PA, Z351 (Box 219)
      - Town Map, Athol, MA, Z352 (Box 219)
      - Map of New Britain, CT, 1912; Z353 (Box 219)
      - Proposed Zone System for Meadow Development, Newark, NJ, Z355 (Box 219)
      - Approach Rand Park, Keshuk, IA, Z356 (Box 219)
      - Dam Across Mississippi River at Keokuk, IA, Z357 (Box 219)
      - Detached Small Cottage, City Planning Study, 1912; Z358 (Box 219)
      - Typical Double House, C.P. Study, Z359 (Box 219)
      - Bird's Eye View, Fitchburg, MA, 1870; Z360 (Box 219)
      - Bird's Eye View, Fitchburg, MA, Population 14,000, 1882; Z361 (Box 219)
      - Proposed Street Changes, Fitchburg, MA, 1912; Z362 (Box 219)
      - Bluff below Summit Ave, Center St. School, Schenectady, NY, Z363 (Box 219)
      - Back Yards, South Bend, IN, Z364 (Box 219)
      - Railroad Station, Cohasset, MA, Z365 (Box 219)
      - Depot Street, Cohasset, MA, Z366 (Box 219)
      - New Railroad Station, Cohasset, MA, Z367 (Box 219)
      - South Main Street, Cohasset, MA, Z368 (Box 219)
      - Street View, Cohasset, MA, Z369 (Box 219)
      - Sunset Rock, Cushing St, Cohasset, MA, Z370 (Box 219)
      - Road, Poles, Cohasset, MA, Z371 (Box 219)
      - Norfolk Road, Cohasset, MA, steep and costly grade, Z372 (Box 219)
      - Turn at Gulf Island, Cohasset, MA, Z373 (Box 219)
      - Plan, Street Intersection, Cohasset, MA, Z374 (Box 219)
      - View Across Commons, Cohasset, MA, Z375 (Box 219)
      - Spring St, Opposite Library, Cohasset, MA, Z376 (Box 219)
      - Post Office, Cohasset, MA, Z377 (Box 219)
      - Fire House, Cohasset, MA, Z378 (Box 219)
      - Grain and Straw Building, Cohasset, MA, Z379 (Box 219)
      - Small Open Space, Cohasset, MA, Z380 (Box 219)
      - Bath Houses, Cohasset, MA, Z381 (Box 219)
      - Bath Houses, Cohasset, MA, Z382 (Box 219)
      - Kimballs Point, a Sandy Beach, Cohasset, MA, Z383 (Box 219)
      - James Brook Region, Cohasset, MA, Z384 (Box 219)
      - Early Survey, Cohasset, MA, Z385 (Box 219)
      - View from Railroad Station, Walpole, MA, Z386 (Box 219)
      - Bird's Hall & Post Office, East Walpole, MA, Z387 (Box 219)
      - Mill & Office (Bird), E. Walpole, MA, Z388 (Box 219)
      - Offices, F.W. Bird & Son, E. Walpole, MA, Z389 (Box 219)
      - Bird School, E. Walpole, MA, Z390 (Box 219)
      - Public School (Bird School), E. Walpole, MA, poor relation to playground, Z391 (Box 219)
      - High School, Walpole, MA, Z392 (Box 219)
      - Near High School, Walpole, MA, Z393 (Box 219)
      - Public Library, Walpole, MA, Z394 (Box 219)
      - Town Hall, Walpole, MA, Z395 (Box 219)
      - First Parish Unitarian Church, Walpole, MA, Z396 (Box 219)
      - New Catholic Church, Walpole, MA, Z397 (Box 219)
      - Common & Fountain, Walpole, MA, Z398 (Box 219)
      - Building Line Problem, Walpole, MA, Z399 (Box 219)
      - Map of Walpole, MA, Z400 (Box 219)
      - Railroad Station, N. Attleboro, MA, Z401 (Box 220)
      - Washington Street, N. Attleboro, MA, Z402 (Box 220)
      - Washington Street, N. Attleboro, MA, Z403 (Box 220)
      - Post Office, N. Attleboro, MA, Z404 (Box 220)
      - Richards Memorial Library, N. Attleboro, MA, Z405 (Box 220)
      - High School, N. Attleboro, MA, Z406 (Box 220)
      - Town Buildings & Implements, N. Attleboro, MA, Z407 (Box 220)
      - Baptist Church & Common, N. Attleboro, MA, Z408 (Box 220)
      - Factory, H.F. Barrows Company, N. Attleboro, MA, Z409 (Box 220)
      - Apartment Houses, N. Attleboro, MA, Z410 (Box 220)
      - Fall's Pond, N. Attleboro, MA, Z411 (Box 220)
      - Fall's Pond, N. Attleboro, MA, Z412 (Box 220)
      - Ten Mile River, N. Attleboro, MA, Z413 (Box 220)
      - General Plan, N. Attleboro, MA, Z414 (Box 220)
      - Bird's Eye View, N. Attleboro, MA, Z415 (Box 220)
      - North Bridge, from Auburn, Lewiston, ME, Z416 (Box 220)
      - Androscoggin River, Lewiston, ME, Z417 (Box 220)
      - Bates Canal, Lewiston, ME, Z418 (Box 220)
      - Bates Manufacturing Company, Lewiston, ME, Z419 (Box 220)
      - Haymarket Square, Lewiston, ME, Z420 (Box 220)
      - City Hall, Lewiston, ME, Z421 (Box 220)
      - City Park, Lewiston, ME, Z422 (Box 220)
      - Lewiston & Auburn, ME, City Maps, Z423 (Box 220)
      - General Plan, Bates College, Lewiston, ME, 1913; Z424 (Box 220)
      - New Dormitory, Bates College, Lewiston, ME, Z425 (Box 220)
      - Main Street, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z426 (Box 220)
      - Main Street & Trolley, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z427 (Box 220)
      - Public School, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z428 (Box 220)
      - Public School & Playground, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z429 (Box 220)
      - College, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z430 (Box 220)
      - General View, Ginter Park, Richmond, VA, Z431 (Box 220)
      - Map of Richmond, VA, Z432 (Box 220)
      - Map, Richmond & Henrico County, VA, Z433 (Box 220)
      - Clarks Pond, Walpole, MA, Z434 (Box 220)
      - Plan of Playground, East Walpole, MA, Z435 (Box 220)
      - East Walpole Playground, The Hollows, MA, Z436 (Box 220)
      - Bird School Grounds, East Walpole, MA, Z437 (Box 220)
      - Greenfield, MA Map, 1913; Z438 (Box 220)
      - Railroad Approach, Bridgeport, CT, 1913; Z439 (Box 220)
      - Main Street & Fairfield Ave. Bridgeport, CT, 1913; Z440 (Box 220)
      - Harbor, Bridgeport, CT, 1913; Z441 (Box 220)
      - High School, Bridgeport, CT, 1913; Z442 (Box 220)
      - Seaside Park, Bridgeport CT, Z443 (Box 220)
      - Plan, Shaker Heights, Cleveland, OH, 1913; Z444 (Box 220)
      - Shaker Heights, Cleveland, OH, relation to city, Z445 (Box 220)
      - Shaker Heights, Cleveland, OH, Street View #3, Z446 (Box 220)
      - Shaker Heights, Cleveland, OH, Curving Street, 1913; Z447 (Box 220)
      - Neponset Garden Village Preliminary Plan, E. Walpole, MA, Z448 (Box 220)
      - City Plan Commission, 1913 - 1914; Z449 (Box 220)
      - City Plan Commission, 1914; Z450 (Box 220)
      - Lord and Lady Aberdeen, Dublin, Ireland, Z451 (Box 221)
      - Plan, Everett, MA and Part of Metropolitan District, Z452 (Box 221)
      - Plan, Everett, MA, Z453 (Box 221)
      - Survey, Davidson College, NC, Z454 (Box 221)
      - Athletic Field, Davidson, NC, Z455 (Box 221)
      - Outdoor Gymnasium, Davidson College, NC, Z456 (Box 221)
      - Cover Page, Factory Magazine, January 1914; Z457 (Box 221)
      - Plan, Washington, PA, Z458 (Box 221)
      - Government Topographic Map, Waterbury, CT, Z459 (Box 221)
      - City Map, Waterbury, CT, 1914; Z460 (Box 221)
      - Housing showing fire hazard, S. Main Street, Waterbury, CT, Z462 (Box 221)
      - Small Single Family House, E. Main Street, Waterbury, CT, Z463 (Box 221)
      - Hillside Houses, Waterbury, CT, Z464 (Box 221)
      - Employees, Thomas B. Jeffery Company, Kenosha, WI, Z465 (Box 221)
      - Kenosha Evening News, Kenosha, WI, Z466 (Box 221)
      - Kenosha, WI City Map, Z467 (Box 221)
      - Growth of Industry, Allen Shoe Industry, Syrin?, Z468 (Box 221)
      - Excess Condemnation, 7th Ave, Plan, New York City, NY, Z469 (Box 221)
      - Excess Condemnation, 7th Ave, Plan, New York City, NY, Z470 (Box 221)
      - Excess Condemnation, 7th Ave, Plan, New York City, NY, Z471 (Box 221)
      - Excess Condemnation, Varick Street, Plan, New York City, NY, Z472 (Box 221)
      - Excess Condemnation, Lafayette Street, Plan, New York City, NY, Z473 (Box 221)
      - Woodlands, Loveland Farm, Youngstown, OH, Z474 (Box 221)
      - Ready-Cut-Houses, Loveland Farms, Youngstown, OH, Z475 (Box 221)
      - Development Work, Loveland Farms, Youngstown, OH, Z476 (Box 221)
      - City Plan, Preliminary, La Crosse, WI, Z477 (Box 221)
      - Housing, Burlington, VT, Z478 (Box 221)
      - Single House, Burlington, VT, Z479 (Box 221)
      - U.S. Topographic, Gardner, MA, Z480 (Box 221)
      - City Map, Gardner, MA, Z481 (Box 221)
      - Street Scene, Gardner, MA, Z482 (Box 221)
      - Old Town Hall, Gardner, MA, Z483 (Box 221)
      - War Monument, Gardner, MA, Z484 (Box 221)
      - Soot Fall in 1912, Pittsburgh, PA, 1912; Z485 (Box 221)
      - Texarkana, TX, Z486 (Box 221)
      - "Dance of the Nymphs" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Discovery of the Hudson" Bierstadt, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Flatford Mill" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Forest of Fontainbleau" J.H. Rousseau, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Le Chateau de Braun" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Le Chateau Saint-Ange" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Madonna" by Titian, Alte Pinakothek, Munich, Germany, 17 (Box 222)
      - "On the Shores of a Lake" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Souvenir of Italy" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "St. Marks Venice" Turner, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Stratford on Avon" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Sunset" Rousseau, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Cornfield" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Cornfield" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Fighting Temeraire" J.M.W. Turner, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Ford" Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Forest Road" Ruisdael, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Glebe Farm" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Hay Wain" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "The Valley Farm" Constable, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Watermill," Hobbema, 17 (Box 222)
      - Corot, 17 (Box 222)
      - Diaz, 17 (Box 222)
      - Ruisdael, 17 (Box 222)
      - "Heidelburg" Turner, 15 (Box 223)
      - Ruysdael, Le Marais. - Musee de l'Ermitage., 343 (Box 223)
      - Ruysdael, La Chasse. - Musee de Dresde., 344 (Box 223)
      - Ruysdael, Le Digues. - Musee du Louvre., 345 (Box 223)
      - Ruysdael, Vue d'une riviere, Amesterdam, v. de Hoop., 347 (Box 223)
      - Van Goyen, Vue de Dordrecht. - Musee d'Amsterdam, 348 (Box 223)
      - P. Potter, La Vache qui se mire. - Musee de La Haye., 364 (Box 223)
      - Turner, Le Pelerinage de Childe Harold. - National Gallery, Londres., 375 (Box 223)
      - Claude Lorrain, Ulisse remet Chryseis a soa pere. - Louvre., 394 (Box 223)
      - Claude Lorrain, Le Midi.- Musee de l'Ermitage., 397 (Box 223)
      - Rousseau, Sortie de foret a Fontainbleau. - Louvre., 446 (Box 223)
      - Daubigny, Bords de l'oise. - Paris., 448 (Box 223)
      - Troyon, Boeufs se rendant au labour. Louvre., 449 (Box 223)
      - Millet, Les Glaneuses. - Louvre., 454 (Box 223)
      - Daubigny, Le printemps. - Musee du Louvre., 611 (Box 223)
      - J. Dupre, La fenaison. Musee du Luxembourg., 837 (Box 223)
      - Lerolle, dans la campagne, Musee de Luxembourg, 838 (Box 223)
      - S. Van Ruysdael, La Halte. - Amsterdam., 997 (Box 223)
      - Claude Lorrain, Paysage italien. - Musee de Berlin., 1020 (Box 223)
      - Julien Dupre, La prairie., 1082 (Box 223)
      - Velasquez, Paysage espagnol. - Musee de la Haye., 1123 (Box 223)
      - Corot, Le chemin montant., 1215 (Box 223)
      - Corot, Le matin sur l'etang, 1218 (Box 223)
      - Millet, La chute des feuilles., 1224 (Box 223)
      - Millet, Le premiers pas., 1227 (Box 223)
      - Salvator Rosa, Raysage. - Florence.\, 1279 (Box 223)
      - Poussin, Paysage. - London., 1283 (Box 223)
      - Gainsborough, L'abreuvoir. - National Gallery, London., 1285 (Box 223)
      - Turner, Le Golfe de Baiae. - National Gallery, London., 1298 (Box 223)
      - Gainsborough, Paysage. - National Gallery, London., 1319 (Box 223)
      - Greuze, Jeune fille, etude. - Musee du Louvre., 1331 (Box 223)